

United Arab Emirates (UAE) +971 5053 86387 villamaryjoy50@gmail.com https://joyhousecare.github.io

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To seek a position wherein I can use my knowledge and skills in working domestic and international job opportunities

Summary

Skilled executive housekeeper with years of experience leading a team of over 20 individuals. Proficient in mentoring new members of the team so everyone always knows what they are supposed to accomplish. Strong interpersonal skills to offer clients the best experience possible from a kind, courteous staff. Able to maintain a level head under high-pressure circumstances and never let the ball drop for a second

Education

Bachelor's Of Science And Public Administration

Eulogio "Amang" Rodriguez (Institute of Science and Technology)

MARY JOY VILLA ALOJADO

WORK EXPERIENCE

CLEANER / TEAM LEAD - 02/2022 to Present **UAE**. Dubai

- Attend to clients enquiries and requests.
- Check cleaning equipment condition.
- Check work done by cleaners.
- Demonstrate understanding of cleaning methods and processes.
- Inform supervisor or manager when stock level of cleaning materials is low.

HOUSE KEEPER - 06/2016 to 09/2021 **Qatar**, Doha

- Create standards for levels of cleanliness that have to be met at every house.
- Check in with clients after a job to ensure their utmost satisfaction with a cleaner's capabilities.
- Maintain quarterly budgets and make adjustments when necessary to ensure a safety net is always in place.
- Train new staff members to abide by the high standards set forth by the company.
- Implemented new marketing program that saw a 20 percent increase in the number of clients for the fiscal year ending in 2016.

SALES LADY IN GREEN HILLS SHOPPING MALL - 06/2010 to 03/2013

- Identifying and maximising revenue from existing customer accounts. Maintaining high levels of product and customer knowledge and participating in training programmes as appropriate.
- Submitting detailed proposals and quotations to customers.
- Providing regular and accurate sales forecast updates to Senior Managers.

RECEPTIONIST IN GOTESCO TWIN TOWERS - 06/2007 to 03/2008

- Ensured that both the Front Office Manager and Reception Supervisors were kept up-to-date of any relevant feedback from guests and, or, other departments.
- Provided professional as well as friendly customer service at all times.
- Assisted other departments whenever needed.